{
    "subject": "resource/David_Baulcombe",
    "predicate": "ontology/award",
    "object": "resource/Massry_Prize",
    "human_readable": "David Baulcombe was awarded the Massry Prize.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9849117994308472,
            "question": "When was David Baulcombe awarded the Massry Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9846072793006897,
            "question": "Is David Baulcombe a recipient of the Massry Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9796186685562134,
            "question": "For what achievement did David Baulcombe receive the Massry Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9238443374633789,
            "question": "Who else has won the Massry Prize besides David Baulcombe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9204965233802795,
            "question": "What prize did David Baulcombe win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9113360643386841,
            "question": "Who was awarded the Massry Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6723568439483643,
            "question": "What are some notable achievements of Massry Prize winners?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5977665781974792,
            "question": "How is the Massry Prize determined?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5888938307762146,
            "question": "What is the significance of the Massry Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5237302184104919,
            "question": "What field is the Massry Prize associated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Baulcombe was awarded the Massry Prize.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6381_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of the Massry Prize?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6381_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the Massry Prize determined?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6381_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable achievements of Massry Prize winners?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6381_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6381_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6381_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6381_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6381_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6381_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6381_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6381_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6381_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6381_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6381_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents support that David Baulcombe received the Massry Prize. Specifically, it states \"2005 co-recipient (with Craig Mello and Andrew Fire) of the Massry Prize, awarded by the Massry Foundation and the University of Southern California\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}